Finding Aid for Jens Jensen Drawings and Papers 1903-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Drawings
  - N
    - Norwegian Hospital, Chicago, Illinois
      - Design and planting plan for grounds of Norwegian Hospital, 1910; NOR1; Ink on tracing paper; location, type of plantings; arbors, seats; signed. 42 x 41 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 56, Folder 68)
  - O
    - O. Torrison Company, Manitowoc, Wisconsin
      - A plat of the subdivision of the property of the O. Torrison Company, 1922; TOR1; Ink on linen; similar to TOR1; unsigned. 71 x 68 cm. Scale: 1"" =30' (Map-case 60, Folder 88)
      - A plat of the subdivision of the property of the O. Torrison Company, 1922; TOR2; Yellow, black ink on linen; property divided into lots; unsigned. 71 x 68 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 60, Folder 88)
      - Sketch showing proposed improvements. Property of Messrs. Torrison, 1916; TOR3; Blueprint; location of buildings, trees, roadways; signed. 60 x 69 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 60, Folder 88)
    - Oak Park, Illinois. High School.
      - Plan of athletic field showing grading and planting for the Oak Park and River Forest Township high school, 1915; OAK1; Pencil, red ink on tracing paper; plan and cross-sections; signed. 105 x 74 cm. Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK1)
      - Detail for tennis courts and running track of the Oak Park and River Forest Township high school, 1916; OAK2; Red, black ink on linen; signed. 46 x 42 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK2)
      - A plan showing the drainage and water supply for the athletic field for the Oak Park and River Forest Township high school, 1916; OAK3; Red, black ink on linen; signed. 107 x 74 cm. Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK3)
      - Planting plan for Oak Park and River Forest Township high school, 1917; OAK4; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type of plantings; at lower right, ""CR.E. del.""; signed. 105 x 73 cm. Scale: 1"" = 16'. (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK4)
    - Oak Park, Illinois. Parks.
      - Village of Oak Park, Ill. Park property, 1913; OAK5; Ink on linen; outline of property bounded by Berkshires, Ridgeland, Division and Elmwood; signed. 116 x 110 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK5)
      - Village of Oak Park, IL Park property, 1913; OAK6; Ink on linen; outline of property bordered by Lake, Ridgeland, North Boulevard and Elmwood; signed. 73 x 63 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK6)
      - Village of Oak Park, IL Park property, 1913; OAK7; Ink on linen; outline of property bordered by Harrson [sic] Place, Gunderson, and East; signed; 102 x 72 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK7)
      - Village of Oak Park, IL Park property, 1913; OAK8; Red, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations, trees, buildings delineated for property bounded by Grove, Ontario, Oak Park and Lake; signed. 92 x 74 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK8)
      - Park No. 2. Village of Oak Park. Park property. Drain and water plan, 1913; OAK9; Ink, pencil on tracing paper; for area bounded by Lake, Ridgeland, and Elmwood; signed. 56 x 52 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK9)
      - Park No. 3...Water and drain plan, 1913; OAK10; Ink, pencil on tracing paper; area bounded by Harrison, Gunderson and East; signed. 76 x 66 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK10)
      - Planting plan for park no. 3. Oak Park Commission., 1913; OAK11; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; area bounded by Harrison, Gunerson, and East; signed. 99 x 72 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK11)
      - Village of Oak Park, IL park property. Plan of topo. survey, 1914; OAK12; Red, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations, trees for property bounded by Ridgeway, Division and Elmood; signed. 107 x 98 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK12)
      - Planting plan. Village of Oak Park...Park property. Park #2, 1913; OAK13; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; area bounded by Lake, Ridgeland, and Elmwood; signed. (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK13)
      - Design for park. Oak Park Commission...Planting plan., 1914; OAK14; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; baseball diamond, tennis courts, seats for area bounded by Ridgeland, Division and Elmwood signed. 91 x 83 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK14)
      - Grounds of Oak Park Commission...Drain and water plan., 1914; OAK15; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; for area bounded by Ridgeland, Division, and Elmwood; signed; 92 x 84 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK15)
      - Village of Oak Park. Park Commission. Plan of tape survey., 1914; OAK16; Ink on linen; location, type of trees; notes; area bounded by Lake, Elmwood, North Blvd. and Scoville; signed; 58 x 64 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK16)
      - Oak Park Commission...Plan for wading pool. Park #3., 1914; OAK17; Ink on linen; plan, sections; signed; 50 x 24 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK17)
      - Water and drainage plan. Park No. 2., 1915; OAK18; Ink, pencil on linen; signed; 106 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK18)
      - Planting plan for park no. 2., 1915; OAK19; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 111 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK19)
      - Planting plan for park no.2., 1915; OAK20; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 112 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK20)
      - Plan of playground...Pyott Playground., 1918; OAK21; Black, red, blue ink, pencil on blueline print; location of proposed reservoir and embankment; unsigned; 88 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK21)
      - Scoville Park...Drain and water plan., 1913; OAK22; Pencil, ink on tracing paper; notes; signed; 74 x 60 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK22)
      - Scoville Park...Planting plan., 1913; OAK23; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; pools, tennis courts; signed; 91 x 75 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 69)
        (neg. # OAK23)
    - Oak Ridge Cemetery, DuPage County, Illinois
      - Oak Ridge Cemetery, 1910; OAM1; Blueprint, pencil; plat of survey, with driveway sketched in pencil; lower right cut away; unsigned; 52 x 58 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
    - Oakhaven Old People's Home, Chicago, Illinois
      - A planting plan for the grounds of the Oakhaven Old People's Home., 1924; OAP1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; unsigned; 61 x 49 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
      - Planting diagram. Oakhaven Old People's Home., 1924; OAP2; Blueprint, pencil additions; Chas D. Faulkner, architect; driveways, areas of plantings indicated; unsigned; 63 x 53 cm.; No scale (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
    - Oates, J.F., Evanston, Illinois
      - Grounds of J.F. Oates, Esq....Planting plan., 1915; OAT1; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; residence by Schmidt, Garden and Martin; signed; 76 x 28 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
    - Oberne, John E., Knoxville, Tennessee (Spencer & Powers, architect)
      - Property of J.E. Oberne., 1917; OBE1; Blueprint; topo. lines, building; locations; unsigned; 54 x 24 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
      - Garden walls, pergola, walks, etc., in connection with house and garage for John E. Oberne., 1917; OBE2; Blueprint; plans, details, sections, elevations; Spencer and Powers, architects; unsigned; 85 x 70 cm.; Scales vary (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
      - Preliminary sketch. Estate of J.E. Oberne, Esq., 1917; OBE3; Pencil on tracing paper; location of plantings, walkways, pool, steps, etc.; unsigned; 140 x 60 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
      - House and garage for John E. Oberne., 1917; OBE4; Blueline; upper right corner torn away; topo. lines, elevations, ""cut"" and ""fill"" instructions; unsigned; 106 x 70 cm.; No scale (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
    - Odell, Benjamin F.J., Kenilworth, Illinois
      - Grounds of Benj. F.J. Odell, Esq....Plan of tape survey., 1914; ODE1; Ink on linen; signed; 56 x 33 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
        (neg. # ODE1)
      - Grounds of Benj. Odell., 1914; ODE2; Ink on linen; planting plan, with location, type, amounts of plantings; gardens, seats; most amounts crossed out in pencil and revised; signed; 56 x 30 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
        (neg. # ODE2)
    - Oppenheimer, H.D., Chicago, Illinois
      - Revised planting design. Grounds of H.D. Oppenheimer., 1910; OPP1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens, pool, seats, trellis, summer house; signed; 56 x 45 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
      - Design for pool, trellis and summer house. Grounds of Mr. Oppenheimer. Hyde Park., 1910; OPP2; Red, black ink on tracing paper; plans, elevations, details; signed; 55 x 25 cm.; Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
      - Plan showing location of trellis, summer house, pool, drains and water pipes. Grounds of Mr. Oppenheimer. Hyde Park., 1910; OPP3; Ink on tracing paper; signed; 55 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 70)
    - Orb, I., Glencoe, Illinois
      - Planting plan and further suggestions for remodeling the estate of I. Orb, Esq., 1904; ORB1; Pencil, ink on linen; location, type of plantings; revisions in pencil; proposed location of formal garden, roadways; planting list; signed; 94 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
    - Ottawa, Illinois. Parks.
      - Illinois State Park Commission...Topo. survey., 1913; OTT1; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; topo. lines; elevations; buildings, pond; unsigned; 100 x 13 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
    - Owen, W. David, Lake Forest, Illinois (Schmidt, Garden & Martin, architects)
      - A planting plan for a portion of the estate of Mr. W. David Owen., 1923; OWE1; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings along driveways; planting list, with botanical and common names, sizes and quantities; signed; 104 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Topographical survey...David B. [sic] Owen Estate., 1923; OWE2; Blueprint, pencil additions; Richard E. Schmidt, Garden and Martin, architects; driveway sketched in pencil; unsigned; 76 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
    - Owen Subdivision, McHenry Co., Illinois
      - Plat of survey of Owen Estate., 1914; OWG1; Blueprint; unsigned; 54 x 42 cm.; No scale (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Plan of topo. survey for the subdivision of the Owen Estate., 1921; OWG2; Pencil, brown, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations, selected trees; signed; 206 x 107 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Section 2: Plan of topo. survey for the subdivision of the Owen Estate., 1921; OWG3; Brown, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations for area around barn and public road; signed; 47 x 23 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - A road and lot plan for the first addition. Owen, Stenger and Allen Subdv., 1921; OWG4; Ink on linen; property divided into lots; area bounded by River, Crescent, John Roads and King property; signed; 81 x 47 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Road and lot plan for the Owen, Stenger, and Allen first addition., 1921; OWG5; Ink on linen; lots numbered; area bounded by River, Crescent, John Rds.; similar to OWG4; signed; 74 x 43 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Untitled, OWG6; Pencil on tracing paper; various distances between points in area along brook; layout for golf course?; unsigned; 135 x 104 cm.; [Scale: 1"" = 50'?] (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Untitled, OWG7; Pencil on tracing paper; area divided into lots; tennis courts, club house; signed (lower right); 203 x 103 cm.; [Scale: 1"" = 50'?] (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Untitled, OWG8; Pencil on tracing paper; nine-hole golf course, with hole-yardage; lots for surrounding subdivisions marked off; unsigned. 140 x 104 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Fox River Golf Club, OWG9; Blueprint; property divided into lots flanking course; unsigned. 55 x 45 cm. Scale; 1"" = 200' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
  - P
    - Pabst, Frederick, Oconomowoc, Wisconsin
      - Map of location of the canal in the E1/2 of section 11 T. 7 N. R. 17 E. Property of Mr. Fred Pabst, 1907; PAB1; Ink on linen; surveyed by William Pomric (?), Waukesha, Wisconsin; unsigned. 75 x 101 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Plan of the new addition to the estate of Fred Pabst, Esq, 1907; PAB2; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; canal, bridge, building, roadway; signed. 93 x 69 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
      - Planting design and ground plan for the country estate of Mr. Frederick Pabst, esq., 1907; PAB3; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens, roadways, paths; signed. 95 x 49 cm. Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 57, Folder 71)
    - Paepcke, Herman, Glencoe, Illinois (Jebson & Fromann, architect)
      - Planting plan. Part I. Country Home of H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE2; Red, orange, blue, green watercolor, black ink on heavy paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; gardens, pond; penciled revisions; signed ""James Jensen."" 80x 64 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Planting plan. Part II (bluff section), PAE3; Orange, green, blue watercolor, black ink on heavy paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; signed ""James Jensen"". 70 x 39 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Planting plan III. H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE4; Orange, green watercolor, black ink on heavy paper; location, type of plantings; signed ""James Jensen"". 89 x 47 cm. No scale (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Topographical survey. H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE5; Red, brown, green, blue watercolor, black ink on heavy paper; topo lines, elevations; plan, profile of elevations; signed. ""James Jensen"". 77 x 65 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Water and sewer system. H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE6; Red, brown, blue watercolor, red, black ink on heavy paper; signed ""James Jensen"". 77 x 68 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Plan of lake bluff and grounds around residence. H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE7; Blueprint; residence by Fromann and Jepsen; signed ""James Jensen"". 77 x 60 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Planting plan. H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE8; Blueprint; location, type, amounts of plantings around residence; signed ""James Jensen""; 73 x 56 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Planting plan. H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE8a; Blueprint; ""key to planting plan""; signed ""James Jensen"". 29 x 20 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Rustic bridge for H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE9; Ink on linen; profiles and detailed sections; signed ""James Jensen"". 87 x 40 cm. Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - [Sketch] for arch for bridge, PAE10; Ink on linen; section, end views; signed ""James Jensen"". 30x 25 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Planting plan. Entrance to country home., 1903; PAE11; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; key to plantings; signed ""Jens Jensen"". 69 x 36 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Planting plan., 1903; PAE12; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed. 86 x 32 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Grounds of Mr. H. Paepcke, PAE13; Ink on linen; location of buildings, roads, ravines, pond; ""copied from plan of 1901""; signed. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Grounds of Mr. Herman Paepcke...Sketch, 1914; PAE14; Pencil on tracing paper; sketch of garden area, with some plantings; location of walkways, chicken coop and runs, compost yard; signed. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Portion of estate of Herman Paepcke, 1914; PAE15; Pencil, ink on linen; elevations; signed. 71 x 45 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Plan of entrance to country home of H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE16; Ink on heavy paper; plan, profiles of entrance to Sheridan Road; signed ""James Jensen"". 76 x 59 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Plan showing change in drive and rustic entrance gateway for H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE17; Ink on linen; similar to PAE16 with plan and profiles of entrance from Sheridan Road; signed ""James Jensen"". 64 x 35 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Proposed changes on the estate of H. Paepcke, Esq, PAE18; Green, brown watercolor, black pencil on heavy paper; present, proposed drives, planting areas, buildings; notes with estimates of various costs (i.e. widening of road $400, new road #200, etc.) and totals; signed ""Jens Jensen"". 83 x 48 cm. Scale: 1"" = 50 (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Untitled, PAE19; Red, black ink on heavy paper; on reverse, ""bluff and grounds around residence""; location of water or drain tiles; location, type of plantings; unsigned. 73 x 63 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
      - Plat showing location of residence for Mr. Herm. Paepcke, PAE20; Blueprint; topo lines, residence outlined in pencil; unsigned. 43 x 70 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 72)
    - Pasadena, California. Parks
      - Planting plan. Central Park, PAS1; Blueprint; location, type of plantings; pool, fountain, buildings; signed ""James Jensen""; 89 x 46 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Planting plan. Central Park, PAS1a; Blueprint; ""Key to planting plan. Central Park...""; signed ""James Jensen."" 35 x 30 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Map of Central Park, PAS2; Blueprint; rectangular area bounded by streets; distances; unsigned. 38 x 65 cm. Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Contour map. Library Park, PAS3; Blueprint; topo lines, elevations, location, type of trees; unsigned. 53 x 61 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Planting plan. Library Park, PAS4; Blueprint; key to plantings on next sheet; signed ""James Jensen"". 60 x 50 cm. Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Key to planting plan. Library Park, PAS5; Blueprint; signed ""James Jensen"". 42 x 31 cm. (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Paw Paw, Illinois. Parks.
      - Planting plan for public park, 1910; PAW1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; section showing grades; signed. 57 x 52 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Paxton, Charles E., Lake Forest, Illinois (Hugh M.G. Garden, architect)
      - Estate of Chas E. Paxton...Topographical survey, 1912; PAX1; Ink on linen; elevations; location, type of some trees; signed. 66 x 74 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Grading plan. Mr. C. F. [sic] Paxton, 1912; PAX2; Ink on linen; some contour lines, notes on grade; signed. 65 x 51 cm. Scale 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Revised planting plan. Grounds of Mr. Chas. E. Paxton., 1912; PAX3; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens, pool; trellises, footpaths, seats; residence by Hugh Garden; signed. 75 x 65 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
        (neg. # JEN-Pax-3)
      - Plan for service wall. Grounds of Mr. Chas E. Paxton, 1912; PAX5; Ink on linen; plan, cross-section, elevation, gate detail; signed. 84 x 40 cm. Scales vary. (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Sketch for garden arbors. Chas E. Paxton, 1912; PAX6; ink on linen; front, side elevations, roof view; signed. 43 x 51 cm. Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Sketch for rustic arbor. Chas E. Paxton, 1912; PAX7; Ink on linen; various views, plans; signed. 126 x 68 cm. Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Paxton, Charles F., Lake Forest, Illinois
      - Garden design for home of Mr. Paxton, Esq, 1909; PAY1; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; pool; unsigned. 36 x 34 cm. Scale: 1"" = 8' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Garden pillars and concrete bench for Mr. Charles F. Paxton, 1909; Pay2; Ink on linen; various views of pillars, bench; details; signed. 46 x 27 cm. Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Landscape design and planting plan for country estate of Mr. Charles F. Paxton., 1909; PAY3; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; pools, tennis court, gardens, orchards; signed. 62 x 73 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Pergola for Mr. Charles F. Paxton, 1909; PAY4; Ink on linen; front, roof views; measurements; signed. 39 x 27 cm. Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Untitled, 1909; PAY5; Red, black ink on linen; identical to PAY4, with roof section and front view of pergola, but without title or date; unsigned. 37 x 27 cm. Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Perkins, Frederick W.
      - Plan for the grounds of Frederick W. Perkins, 1921; PER1; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; tennis court, buildings, gardens, arbors; signed. 86 x 49 cm. Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Buildings and grounds. Frederick W. Perkins, 1921; PER2; Ink, pencil on tracing paper; sketch of plantings, types, gardens; unsigned. 90 x 55 cm. Scale: 1/16"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Perry, Norman, Culver, Indiana
      - Proposed plan, as with purchased land., 1928; PET1; Pencil on tracing paper; buildings, gardens, rockwork, plantings; portion of client's name cut away; unsigned. 83 x 97 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Untitled, 1928; PET2; Pencil on tracing paper; sketch of plan with topo lines, elevations, gardens, buildings; unsigned. 83 x 100 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Pick, Albert, Winnetka, Illinois
      - A planting plan for the grounds of Mr. Albert Pick, 1926; PIC1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; footpaths, steps, seats; notes; signed. 44 x 57 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - No title, 1926; PIC2; Pencil on heavy paper; plan of grounds, with drives, buildings; unsigned. 100 x 56 cm. No scale. (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Pick, George, Highland Park, Illinois (Howard Van Doren Shaw, architect)
      - Planting plan. Estate of George Pick, Esq., 1915; PIE1; Red, black on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens footpaths; ""del F.E.H.""; signed. 114 x 62 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - A planting plan for the estate of George Pick, Esq., 1916; PIE2; Ink on linen; more detail around residence than PIE1; location, type of plantings; pools, rockwork, arbor; signed. 87 x 81 cm. Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
      - Untitled, PIE3; Black, red ink, pencil on linen; topo. survey; house and driveway; residence by Howard Shaw; unsigned. 120 x 60 cm. Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 57, Folder 73)
    - Plymouth, Indiana. Lincoln High School.
      - High school building... Plot plan... Index to drawings... Schedule of symbols, 1922; PLY1; Blueprint; Miller, Fullenwider, and Dowling, architects; Ernest W. Young, associate architect; original signed by Dowling; 71 x 69 cm; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 57, Folder 74)
      - High School Building... Details of wall rail... First floor plan... Typical stair details (sheet 6), 1922; PLY2; Blueprint; Miller, Fullenwider, and Dowling, architects; original signed by Dowling; 70 x 69 cm; Scales vary (Map-case 57, Folder 74)
      - A plan showing the design for the brick walks for the Lincoln High School, 1925; PLY3; Ink on linen; unsigned; 64 x 24 cm; Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 57, Folder 74)